[
  {
    "title": "Design Principles",
    "catIndex": "0",
    "entries": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question" : "Time to market",
        "answers": ["Low Priority", "Medium Priority", "High Priority"]
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question" : "Cost Consideration",
        "answers"  : ["Budget Constraint", "Optimum", "No Budget Constraint"]
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question" : "Quality Level",
        "answers"  : ["POC/MVP", "Good Quality", "High Standards"]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question" : "Process Maturity",
        "answers"  : ["Innovation", "Mature", "Packaged"]
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question" : "Innovative Delivery",
        "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Medium", "High"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question" : "Rank the Sustainability",
		    "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Important", "Highly Important"]
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question" : "Rank the Governance",
		    "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Important", "Highly Important"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Project Characteristics",
    "catIndex": "1",
    "entries": [
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question" : "Team Size",
		    "answers"  : ["Small", "Medium", "Large"]
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question" : "Expected Timeline",
		    "answers"  : ["Short", "Long", "Long Term"]
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question" : "CIA Ratings",
		    "answers"  : ["Low", "Medium", "High"]
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "question" : "Domain Intensity",
		    "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Heavy", "Very Heavy"]
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "question" : "Packaged Solution",
		    "answers"  : ["Not Packaged", "Packaged", "Tailored Package"]
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "question" : "Legacy Dominance",
		    "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Medium", "High"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Sourcing Requirement",
    "catIndex": "2",
    "entries": [
      {
        "id": 14,
        "question" : "Complexity",
		    "answers"  : ["Simple", "Fair", "High"]
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "question" : "Ease of Collaboration",
		    "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Important", "Highly Important"]
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "question" : "Cultural Alignment",
		    "answers"  : ["Neutral", "Important", "Highly Important"]
      },
      {
        "id": 17,
        "question" : "Incumbent Transition",
		    "answers"  : ["No Priority", "Priority", "High Priority"]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "Miscellaneous Questions",
    "catIndex": "3",
    "entries": [
      {
        "id": 18,
        "question" : "Required language",
		    "answers"  : ["Dutch", "English"]
      },
      {
        "id": 19,
        "question" : "Documentation language",
		    "answers"  : ["Dutch", "English"]
      },
      {
        "id": 20,
        "question" : "Data requirement standards",
		    "answers"  : ["National", "European", "International"]
      },
      {
        "id": 21,
        "question" : "Compliance and Regulation standards",
		    "answers"  : ["National", "European", "International"]
      },
      {
        "id": 22,
        "question" : "Technology type",
		    "answers"  : ["Legacy", "New"]
      },
      {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Tech category",
        "answers": [[           "UX Design",
            "Mobile Development",
            "Data Engineering",
            "Data Insights",
            "Service & Configuration Management",
            "Digital Marketing Automation",
            "Robotic Process Automation",
            "Business Process Automation",
            "Cloud Apps Engineering",
            "Hyper Scalers",
            "Digital Workplace",
            "API",
            "Streaming",
            "Solution Architecture",
            "Test Automation",
            "DevOps",
            "Application Modernisation",
            "Machine Learning",
            "Low Coding Application Platform",
            "Core Banking",
            "CRM",
            "Payments",
            "ERP",
            "Cyber Security",
            "Banking & Capital Markets",
            "Enterprise Content Management",
            "Cloud Platform Engineering",
            "Digital Work Place",
            "Green Coding",
            "Distribute Ledger",
            "Banking & Capital Market",
            "Domain Knowledge IB",
            "Business Project Management",
            "Project Management Office",
            "Agile Coaches",
            "Architecture & Delivery Management",
            "Big Data & Cloud",
            "Classic BI",
            "Data Visualisation",
            "Cloud Architecture",
            "MS Dynamics",
            "Salesforce"]]
      }
    ]
  }
]
